<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>PlayStation 4 &#8211; Video Game Warehouse</title>
	<atom:link href="/VGW/product-category/ps4/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/VGW</link>
	<description>Buy New &#38; Used Video Games</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 18:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Crew: Wild Run &#8211; PlayStation 4</title>
		<link>/VGW/product/the-crew-wild-run-playstation-4/</link>
		<comments>/VGW/product/the-crew-wild-run-playstation-4/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[webmaster]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/VGW/product/the-crew-wild-run-playstation-4/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Price:29.99 <br /><img width="1181" height="1500" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/1488844855_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" />Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. Item specifics Condition: Good : An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, or to the item cover including scuffs, scratches, or cracks. The cover art and liner notes are included for a CD. VHS or DVD box is included. Video game instructions are included. No skipping on CD/DVD. No fuzzy/snowy frames on VHS tape. See the seller’s listing for full details and description of any imperfections. See all condition definitions&#8211; opens in a new window or tab Seller Notes: &#8220;GAME DISK ONLY! Every game we sell is GUARANTEED TO WORK! May have markings, discoloration, scratches, or other cosmetic flaws. This does not affect gameplay.&#8221; Platform: Sony PlayStation 4 Rating: T &#8211; Teen Release Year: 2014 Genre: Racing MPN: 35863 Game Name: The Crew UPC: 887256300920 The Crew: Wild Run (Sony PlayStation 4, 2014) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!! Detailed item info Product Information Players join their friends for massively multiplayer open-world racing and take on the role of an undercover agent who attempts to infiltrate an illegal street-racing gang in The Crew. The action is designed to offer a seamless, arcade-style glimpse at the entire continental United States, with trips from New York to Los Angeles taking roughly 90 minutes. There are more than a dozen cities and iconic locations to visit along the way, including Miami Beach, the National Mall, and the Las Vegas Strip, and gamers can transition from a single-player adventure to multiplayer action at any time. As gamers explore the country they can take on a variety of races, challenges, and mini-games, with any player they meet potentially becoming a rival, or a member of their four-man crew. In addition to traditional races on defined courses against up to seven others, players can take on special missions that find them racing from one point to another as quickly as possible, collecting items scattered across the map, fleeing cops or a rival crew, tailing allies or targets, using their cars as a battering ram to take down opposition vehicles, or racing against the clock and passing through checkpoints to gain precious seconds. Multiplayer fans can cooperate and compete at the same time, teaming up to meet a common goal while at the same time vying to earn more money, parts, and experience than their teammates. Completing missions gives gamers the opportunity to buy performance and cosmetic upgrades for their vehicles, and each piece of equipment can be leveled several times. The Crew is not limited to highways and paved roads, as gamers can also specifically tailor their car for track races, off-road rallies, and full contact missions that see them climb over the sand dunes of northern Michigan, kick up plumes of red dust of Monument Valley, and slide through the snowy mountains of Colorado. Players can also take on a variety of timed Skills challenges, which find them climbing to the highest point possible, hitting ramps and landing in the center of a target, and finding as many items as possible, among other activities. Product Highlights Video Product Identifiers Publisher Ubisoft Game The Crew MPN 35863 UPC 887256300920 Key Features Platform Sony PlayStation 4 ESRB Rating T &#8211; Teen Genre Racing Location USA Tech Details ESRB Descriptor Language, Mild Blood, Mild Suggestive Themes, Violence Release Year 2014 Game Special Features Take on races, missions, and mini-games while travelling across the entire continental United States Form crews of four to complete missions, earn experience, and upgrade a car&#8217;s look and performance Seamlessly transition from solo missions to multiplayer action against up to seven competitors View on eBay</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/the-crew-wild-run-playstation-4/">The Crew: Wild Run &#8211; PlayStation 4</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br>Price:29.99 <br><img width="1181" height="1500" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/1488844855_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" /><hr /> Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. </p>
<hr />
 </p>
<div class="itemAttr">
<div class="section">
<h2 class="secHd">Item specifics</h2>
<table id="itmSellerDesc" width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr>
<th>Condition:</th>
<td style="width: 92%;"><b>Good</b> 	     		<b>:</b> 	     			<span class="padL"> 						<a id="itmCondOlyhlpIcon"> 							<span class="itmDescQbbl" role="img" aria-label="Help overlay dialog is opened."></span> 						</a> 					</span>										 					</p>
<div class="oly_upnl" id="itmCondDscOly">
<div style="padding: 5px 10px 10px;"> 						  	An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, or to the item cover including scuffs, scratches, or cracks. The cover art and liner notes are included for a CD. VHS or DVD box is included. Video game instructions are included. No skipping on CD/DVD. No fuzzy/snowy frames on VHS tape. See the seller’s listing for full details and description of any imperfections.<a href="http://pages.ebay.com/help/sell/contextual/condition_7.html" target="_blank" class="infoLink u-nowrap" > 									See all condition definitions<b class="g-hdn">&#8211; opens in a new window or tab</b></a> 							</div></div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<th>Seller Notes:</th>
<td class="sellerNotesContent"><font class="viDescQuotes">&ldquo;</font><span class="viSNotesCnt">GAME DISK ONLY! Every game we sell is GUARANTEED TO WORK! May have markings, discoloration, scratches, or other cosmetic flaws. This does not affect gameplay.</span><font class="viDescQuotes">&rdquo;</font></td>
</tr>
</table>
<table width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Platform: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Sony PlayStation 4</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Rating: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>T &#8211; Teen</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Release Year: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>2014</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Genre: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Racing</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			MPN: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="mpn">35863</h2>
</td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Game Name: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>The Crew</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			UPC: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="gtin13">887256300920</h2>
</td>
</tr>
<p> 							<!-- Added for see review link --> 							</table>
</p></div></div>
<p>The Crew: Wild Run (Sony PlayStation 4, 2014) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!!</p>
<div class="prodDetailDesc">
<div class="prodDetailSec">
<div class="section-ttl">
<h3 class="p_det_title">Detailed item info</h3>
<div class="rd-sep"></div>
</div>
<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td><?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?></p>
<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" border="0" width="100%">
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Information</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Players join their friends for massively multiplayer open-world racing and take on the role of an undercover agent who attempts to infiltrate an illegal street-racing gang in The Crew. The action is designed to offer a seamless, arcade-style glimpse at the entire continental United States, with trips from New York to Los Angeles taking roughly 90 minutes. There are more than a dozen cities and iconic locations to visit along the way, including Miami Beach, the National Mall, and the Las Vegas Strip, and gamers can transition from a single-player adventure to multiplayer action at any time.</p>
<p>As gamers explore the country they can take on a variety of races, challenges, and mini-games, with any player they meet potentially becoming a rival, or a member of their four-man crew. In addition to traditional races on defined courses against up to seven others, players can take on special missions that find them racing from one point to another as quickly as possible, collecting items scattered across the map, fleeing cops or a rival crew, tailing allies or targets, using their cars as a battering ram to take down opposition vehicles, or racing against the clock and passing through checkpoints to gain precious seconds. Multiplayer fans can cooperate and compete at the same time, teaming up to meet a common goal while at the same time vying to earn more money, parts, and experience than their teammates.</p>
<p>Completing missions gives gamers the opportunity to buy performance and cosmetic upgrades for their vehicles, and each piece of equipment can be leveled several times. The Crew is not limited to highways and paved roads, as gamers can also specifically tailor their car for track races, off-road rallies, and full contact missions that see them climb over the sand dunes of northern Michigan, kick up plumes of red dust of Monument Valley, and slide through the snowy mountains of Colorado. Players can also take on a variety of timed Skills challenges, which find them climbing to the highest point possible, hitting ramps and landing in the center of a target, and finding as many items as possible, among other activities.</font><br class="br"/><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Highlights</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Video</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<div id="webyclipEmbeded" webyclip-product-page-title="The Crew (Sony PlayStation 4, 2014)" webyclip-product-name="The Crew Sony PlayStation 4" webyclip-external-id="181989722" webyclip-category="Video Games" webyclip-subcategory="US"></div>
<p><script type="text/javascript"> (function() { var s = document.createElement('script'); s.type = 'text/javascript'; s.async = true; s.src = (("https:" == document.location.protocol) ? "https://6bf746ad5bc91a240a3d-1d8fbdf7ecdc2b67730d7c561f0d1dfd.ssl.cf2.rackcdn.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js" : "http://code.webyclip.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js"); var x = document.getElementsByTagName('script')[0]; x.parentNode.insertBefore(s, x); })(); </script></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Identifiers</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Publisher</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Ubisoft</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">The Crew</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">MPN</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">35863</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">UPC</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">887256300920</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Key Features</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Platform</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Sony PlayStation 4</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Rating</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">T &#8211; Teen</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Genre</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Racing</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Location</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">USA</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Tech Details</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Descriptor</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Language, Mild Blood, Mild Suggestive Themes, Violence</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Release Year</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">2014</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game Special Features</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<li>Take on races, missions, and mini-games while travelling across the entire continental United States
<li>Form crews of four to complete missions, earn experience, and upgrade a car&#8217;s look and performance
<li>Seamlessly transition from solo missions to multiplayer action against up to seven competitors
<p></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
</table>
</td>
</tr>
</table></div></div>
<p> <a href="http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?ff3=2&#038;toolid=10039&#038;campid=5337897552&#038;item=172522258388&#038;vectorid=229466">View on eBay </a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/the-crew-wild-run-playstation-4/">The Crew: Wild Run &#8211; PlayStation 4</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/VGW/product/the-crew-wild-run-playstation-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	
<product>
	<price>29.99 </price>
<image>/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/1488844855_s-l1600_700x700_thumb-300x300.jpg</image>
</product>

	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Natural Doctrine &#8211; PlayStation 4</title>
		<link>/VGW/product/natural-doctrine-playstation-4/</link>
		<comments>/VGW/product/natural-doctrine-playstation-4/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[webmaster]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/VGW/product/natural-doctrine-playstation-4/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Price:24.99 <br /><img width="1202" height="1500" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/1489537143_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" />Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. Item specifics Condition: Good : An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, or to the item cover including scuffs, scratches, or cracks. The cover art and liner notes are included for a CD. VHS or DVD box is included. Video game instructions are included. No skipping on CD/DVD. No fuzzy/snowy frames on VHS tape. See the seller’s listing for full details and description of any imperfections. See all condition definitions&#8211; opens in a new window or tab Seller Notes: &#8220;GAME DISK ONLY! Every game we sell is GUARANTEED TO WORK! May have markings, discoloration, scratches, or other cosmetic flaws. This does not affect gameplay.&#8221; Platform: Sony PlayStation 4 Rating: M &#8211; Mature Release Year: 2014 Genre: Role Playing MPN: 813633014036 Game Name: Natural Doctrine UPC: 813633014036 Natural Doctrine (Sony PlayStation 4, 2014) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!! Detailed item info Product Information A turn-based strategy title designed to be very challenging, Natural Doctrine sends players into mines to acquire the valuable resource Pluton and gain access to Feste, the last human city in the world. Pluton is magical, finite, and toxic to humans, but goblins can refine it into a safer form, which leads to frequent attacks from explorers known as Bergmans. Gamers take control of several of these Bergmans, using close-quarters combat, ranged attacks, magic, and firearms to battle goblins, orcs, lizardfolk, minotaurs, wyverns, dragons, and continually evolving monsters known as gorians. Players can examine the battlefields from third-person, top-down, and isometric viewpoints, and instead of grids, each map is divided into larger geometric areas, with blue lines marking off attack zones, and red lines delineating enemy territory. Characters can travel freely through these areas, with objects, destructible areas, and differences in elevation sometimes offering a competitive advantage, and multiple characters can occupy the same area to perform powerful Link Turn combo attacks. Gamers must use extreme caution at all times because the total amount of Pluton available in the game is fixed, and if any member of the party dies in battle, the game is over. Solo gamers can take on Story Missions to advance the plot, or try Free Missions to gain more experience and equipment, heading to the World Map in between battles to change the formation of their group, outfit their allies, develop new skills, and save their game. Natural Doctrine also offers cross-platform online multiplayer action for PS3, PS4, and Vita, and Ad-hoc multiplayer for Vita users. Multiplayer battles unfold in the same way as single-player battles, but gamers form their party by collecting cards and building a custom deck, and then using Card Points they accrue to improve their characters or buy better cards. Product Highlights Video Product Identifiers Publisher NIS America Game Natural Doctrine UPC 813633014036 Key Features Platform Sony PlayStation 4 ESRB Rating M &#8211; Mature Genre RPG Location USA Tech Details ESRB Descriptor Blood, Violence Control Elements Gamepad/Joystick Number of Players 1-2 Release Year 2014 Game Special Features Engage in turn-based battles with a variety of mythical creatures to acquire valuable Pluton Unleash close-quarters, ranged, magic, firearm, and combination attacks Join friends for multiplayer card collecting and battles View on eBay</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/natural-doctrine-playstation-4/">Natural Doctrine &#8211; PlayStation 4</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br>Price:24.99 <br><img width="1202" height="1500" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/1489537143_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" /><hr /> Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. </p>
<hr />
 </p>
<div class="itemAttr">
<div class="section">
<h2 class="secHd">Item specifics</h2>
<table id="itmSellerDesc" width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr>
<th>Condition:</th>
<td style="width: 92%;"><b>Good</b> 	     		<b>:</b> 	     			<span class="padL"> 						<a id="itmCondOlyhlpIcon"> 							<span class="itmDescQbbl" role="img" aria-label="Help overlay dialog is opened."></span> 						</a> 					</span>										 					</p>
<div class="oly_upnl" id="itmCondDscOly">
<div style="padding: 5px 10px 10px;"> 						  	An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, or to the item cover including scuffs, scratches, or cracks. The cover art and liner notes are included for a CD. VHS or DVD box is included. Video game instructions are included. No skipping on CD/DVD. No fuzzy/snowy frames on VHS tape. See the seller’s listing for full details and description of any imperfections.<a href="http://pages.ebay.com/help/sell/contextual/condition_7.html" target="_blank" class="infoLink u-nowrap" > 									See all condition definitions<b class="g-hdn">&#8211; opens in a new window or tab</b></a> 							</div></div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<th>Seller Notes:</th>
<td class="sellerNotesContent"><font class="viDescQuotes">&ldquo;</font><span class="viSNotesCnt">GAME DISK ONLY! Every game we sell is GUARANTEED TO WORK! May have markings, discoloration, scratches, or other cosmetic flaws. This does not affect gameplay.</span><font class="viDescQuotes">&rdquo;</font></td>
</tr>
</table>
<table width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Platform: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Sony PlayStation 4</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Rating: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>M &#8211; Mature</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Release Year: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>2014</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Genre: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Role Playing</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			MPN: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="mpn">813633014036</h2>
</td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Game Name: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Natural Doctrine</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			UPC: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="gtin13">813633014036</h2>
</td>
</tr>
<p> 							<!-- Added for see review link --> 							</table>
</p></div></div>
<p>Natural Doctrine (Sony PlayStation 4, 2014) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!!</p>
<div class="prodDetailDesc">
<div class="prodDetailSec">
<div class="section-ttl">
<h3 class="p_det_title">Detailed item info</h3>
<div class="rd-sep"></div>
</div>
<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td><?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?></p>
<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" border="0" width="100%">
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Information</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">A turn-based strategy title designed to be very challenging, Natural Doctrine sends players into mines to acquire the valuable resource Pluton and gain access to Feste, the last human city in the world. Pluton is magical, finite, and toxic to humans, but goblins can refine it into a safer form, which leads to frequent attacks from explorers known as Bergmans. Gamers take control of several of these Bergmans, using close-quarters combat, ranged attacks, magic, and firearms to battle goblins, orcs, lizardfolk, minotaurs, wyverns, dragons, and continually evolving monsters known as gorians.</p>
<p>Players can examine the battlefields from third-person, top-down, and isometric viewpoints, and instead of grids, each map is divided into larger geometric areas, with blue lines marking off attack zones, and red lines delineating enemy territory. Characters can travel freely through these areas, with objects, destructible areas, and differences in elevation sometimes offering a competitive advantage, and multiple characters can occupy the same area to perform powerful Link Turn combo attacks. Gamers must use extreme caution at all times because the total amount of Pluton available in the game is fixed, and if any member of the party dies in battle, the game is over.</p>
<p>Solo gamers can take on Story Missions to advance the plot, or try Free Missions to gain more experience and equipment, heading to the World Map in between battles to change the formation of their group, outfit their allies, develop new skills, and save their game. Natural Doctrine also offers cross-platform online multiplayer action for PS3, PS4, and Vita, and Ad-hoc multiplayer for Vita users. Multiplayer battles unfold in the same way as single-player battles, but gamers form their party by collecting cards and building a custom deck, and then using Card Points they accrue to improve their characters or buy better cards.</font><br class="br"/><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Highlights</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Video</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<div id="webyclipEmbeded" webyclip-product-page-title="Natural Doctrine (Sony PlayStation 4, 2014)" webyclip-product-name="natural doctrine sony playstation 4" webyclip-external-id="194334457" webyclip-category="Video Games" webyclip-subcategory="US"></div>
<p><script type="text/javascript"> (function() { var s = document.createElement('script'); s.type = 'text/javascript'; s.async = true; s.src = (("https:" == document.location.protocol) ? "https://6bf746ad5bc91a240a3d-1d8fbdf7ecdc2b67730d7c561f0d1dfd.ssl.cf2.rackcdn.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js" : "http://code.webyclip.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js"); var x = document.getElementsByTagName('script')[0]; x.parentNode.insertBefore(s, x); })(); </script></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Identifiers</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Publisher</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">NIS America</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Natural Doctrine</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">UPC</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">813633014036</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Key Features</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Platform</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Sony PlayStation 4</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Rating</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">M &#8211; Mature</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Genre</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">RPG</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Location</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">USA</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Tech Details</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Descriptor</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Blood, Violence</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Control Elements</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Gamepad/Joystick</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Number of Players</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">1-2</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Release Year</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">2014</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game Special Features</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<li>Engage in turn-based battles with a variety of mythical creatures to acquire valuable Pluton
<li>Unleash close-quarters, ranged, magic, firearm, and combination attacks
<li>Join friends for multiplayer card collecting and battles
<p></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
</table>
</td>
</tr>
</table></div></div>
<p> <a href="http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?ff3=2&#038;toolid=10039&#038;campid=5337897552&#038;item=172530627280&#038;vectorid=229466">View on eBay </a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/natural-doctrine-playstation-4/">Natural Doctrine &#8211; PlayStation 4</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/VGW/product/natural-doctrine-playstation-4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	
<product>
	<price>24.99 </price>
<image>/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/1489537143_s-l1600_700x700_thumb-300x300.jpg</image>
</product>

	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
