<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>PlayStation 1 &#8211; Video Game Warehouse</title>
	<atom:link href="/VGW/product-category/ps1/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/VGW</link>
	<description>Buy New &#38; Used Video Games</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 18:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Need for Speed: High Stakes &#8211; PlayStation 1</title>
		<link>/VGW/product/need-for-speed-high-stakes-playstation-1/</link>
		<comments>/VGW/product/need-for-speed-high-stakes-playstation-1/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 19:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[webmaster]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/VGW/product/need-for-speed-high-stakes-playstation-1/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Price:12.99 <br /><img width="650" height="650" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/1487790667_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" />Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. Item specifics Condition: Good: An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, Platform: Sony PlayStation 1 Rating: E &#8211; Everyone Release Year: 1999 Genre: Racing MPN: 014633079746 Game Name: Need for Speed: High Stakes UPC: 014633079746 Need for Speed: High Stakes (Sony PlayStation 1, 1999) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!! Detailed item info Product Information The fourth title in Electronic Arts&#8217; Need for Speed series on PlayStation, Need for Speed: High Stakes features 19 high-performance sports cars to collect and customize. Play modes include Test Drive, Single Race, Special Events, Hot Pursuit, and High Stakes. You begin with 20,000 credits and will initially be able to access three fictitious tracks in Germany, France, and Canada. To unlock more tracks and vehicles, you must place within the top three of each race in a total of six tournaments. Need for Speed: High Stakes includes visible car damage that affects how your vehicle performs during a race. Hot Pursuit mode picks up where 1998&#8217;s game left off, only this time you can play as the police and chase a series of speed-violators within a time limit. For every lawbreaker you nab, more seconds will be added to the clock. Special Events is a series of eight races, while Test Drive is a practice run to familiarize yourself with each available course. High Stakes mode lets you prove your driving prowess against a second player with your car on the line. The catch? Drivers who lose the race will automatically have their car erased and added to their opponent&#8217;s memory card. Customization features include three difficulty levels, two transmission types, and vehicle upgrades in three areas: suspension and tires, engine and brakes, and improved aerodynamics. Weather is also adjustable, as are traffic conditions and time of day. Product Highlights Video Product Identifiers Publisher Electronic Arts Game Need for Speed: High Stakes MPN 014633079746 UPC 014633079746 Key Features Platform Sony PlayStation 1 ESRB Rating E &#8211; Everyone Genre Racing Location USA Tech Details Control Elements Gamepad/Joystick, Steering Wheel Number of Players 1-2 Release Year 1999 Game Special Features Featured vehicles include a Porsche 911, Chevrolet Corvette, Ferrari F50, McLaren F1 GTR, and a Lamborghini Diablo SV Nab speedsters as a member of law enforcement in the revamped Hot Pursuit mode Customize traffic, weather, and time of day Game Series Need for Speed Series View on eBay</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/need-for-speed-high-stakes-playstation-1/">Need for Speed: High Stakes &#8211; PlayStation 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br>Price:12.99 <br><img width="650" height="650" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/1487790667_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" /><hr /> Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. </p>
<hr />
 </p>
<div class="itemAttr">
<div class="section">
<h2 class="secHd">Item specifics</h2>
<table width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Condition:</td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<!-- ITEM CONDITION  --> 														<!-- If Attribute is having hidden text / link	 -->			 															</p>
<div aria-live="polite"> 															 															 																Good: <span id="vi-cond-addl-info">An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, </span> 																</td>
<p> 																		 																		<!-- TODO: remove hardcoded ID --> 																		</td>
</p></div>
<p> 															 														<!-- </td>

 --> 													</td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Platform: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Sony PlayStation 1</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Rating: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>E &#8211; Everyone</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Release Year: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>1999</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Genre: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Racing</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			MPN: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="mpn">014633079746</h2>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Game Name: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Need for Speed: High Stakes</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			UPC: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="gtin13">014633079746</h2>
</td>
</tr>
<p> 							<!-- Added for see review link --> 							</table>
</p></div></div>
<p>Need for Speed: High Stakes (Sony PlayStation 1, 1999) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!!</p>
<div class="prodDetailDesc">
<div class="prodDetailSec">
<div class="section-ttl">
<h3 class="p_det_title">Detailed item info</h3>
<div class="rd-sep"></div>
</div>
<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td><?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?></p>
<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" border="0" width="100%">
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Information</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">The fourth title in Electronic Arts&#8217; Need for Speed series on PlayStation, Need for Speed: High Stakes features 19 high-performance sports cars to collect and customize. Play modes include Test Drive, Single Race, Special Events, Hot Pursuit, and High Stakes. You begin with 20,000 credits and will initially be able to access three fictitious tracks in Germany, France, and Canada. To unlock more tracks and vehicles, you must place within the top three of each race in a total of six tournaments.</p>
<p>Need for Speed: High Stakes includes visible car damage that affects how your vehicle performs during a race. Hot Pursuit mode picks up where 1998&#8217;s game left off, only this time you can play as the police and chase a series of speed-violators within a time limit. For every lawbreaker you nab, more seconds will be added to the clock. Special Events is a series of eight races, while Test Drive is a practice run to familiarize yourself with each available course.</p>
<p>High Stakes mode lets you prove your driving prowess against a second player with your car on the line. The catch? Drivers who lose the race will automatically have their car erased and added to their opponent&#8217;s memory card. Customization features include three difficulty levels, two transmission types, and vehicle upgrades in three areas: suspension and tires, engine and brakes, and improved aerodynamics. Weather is also adjustable, as are traffic conditions and time of day.</font><br class="br"/><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Highlights</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Video</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<div id="webyclipEmbeded" webyclip-product-page-title="Need for Speed: High Stakes (Sony PlayStation 1, 1999)" webyclip-product-name="need for speed: high stakes sony playstation 1" webyclip-external-id="2022" webyclip-category="Video Games" webyclip-subcategory="US"></div>
<p><script type="text/javascript"> (function() { var s = document.createElement('script'); s.type = 'text/javascript'; s.async = true; s.src = (("https:" == document.location.protocol) ? "https://6bf746ad5bc91a240a3d-1d8fbdf7ecdc2b67730d7c561f0d1dfd.ssl.cf2.rackcdn.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js" : "http://code.webyclip.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js"); var x = document.getElementsByTagName('script')[0]; x.parentNode.insertBefore(s, x); })(); </script></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Identifiers</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Publisher</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Electronic Arts</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Need for Speed: High Stakes</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">MPN</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">014633079746</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">UPC</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">014633079746</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Key Features</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Platform</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Sony PlayStation 1</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Rating</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">E &#8211; Everyone</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Genre</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Racing</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Location</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">USA</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Tech Details</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Control Elements</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Gamepad/Joystick, Steering Wheel</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Number of Players</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">1-2</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Release Year</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">1999</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game Special Features</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<li>Featured vehicles include a Porsche 911, Chevrolet Corvette, Ferrari F50, McLaren F1 GTR, and a Lamborghini Diablo SV
<li>Nab speedsters as a member of law enforcement in the revamped Hot Pursuit mode
<li>Customize traffic, weather, and time of day
<p></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game Series</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Need for Speed Series</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
</table>
</td>
</tr>
</table></div></div>
<p> <a href="http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?ff3=2&#038;toolid=10039&#038;campid=5337897552&#038;item=172388214722&#038;vectorid=229466">View on eBay </a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/need-for-speed-high-stakes-playstation-1/">Need for Speed: High Stakes &#8211; PlayStation 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/VGW/product/need-for-speed-high-stakes-playstation-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	
<product>
	<price>12.99 </price>
<image>/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/1487790667_s-l1600-300x300.jpg</image>
</product>

	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes &#8211; PlayStation 1</title>
		<link>/VGW/product/duke-nukem-land-of-the-babes-playstation-1/</link>
		<comments>/VGW/product/duke-nukem-land-of-the-babes-playstation-1/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 22:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[webmaster]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/VGW/product/duke-nukem-land-of-the-babes-playstation-1/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Price:28.99 <br /><img width="600" height="601" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/1487801677_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" />Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. Item specifics Condition: Good: An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, Platform: Sony PlayStation 1 Rating: M &#8211; Mature Release Year: 2000 Genre: Shooter MPN: 742725207103 Game Name: Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes UPC: 742725207103 Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes (Sony PlayStation 1, 2000) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!! Detailed item info Product Information Duke Nukem has finally scored his dream mission: to protect a gorgeous group of babes whiles saving the world. The Unified Babe Resistance is a group of escapees running from an alien colony&#8217;s hybridization wrath. These aliens are set for a full-scale invasion on Earth with an agenda including the eradication of the male population and the enslaving of beautiful women. It&#8217;s time to rock. Featuring high-resolution 3D environments, Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes is a third-person adventure filled with alien scum and lots of babes. With four unique training areas and six multiplayer arenas, a total of 24 levels included (14 of which are actual missions). Utilizing his time portal, Duke will traverse through alien landscapes, intricate sewer systems, warehouses, and the ever-popular strip clubs in which he frequents. In addition to optional auto aiming, Duke will automatically open doors and climb upon short ledges.This allows the player to focus on the more important aspects of the game such as rescuing babes and solving puzzles. Duke can also swim through water, climb up ladders and walls, and explore the confines of zero gravity movement. Rather than featuring a conventional health system, Duke is judged by an all-new Ego system. Depending on his actions, the Ego meter will either rise after finishing a specific mission or drop on a misfired babe. Think before you shoot&#8230;Duke and the world&#8217;s survival is depending on it. Remaining true to the series, Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes supplies you with a heavy arsenal of weaponry including the blaster, grenade launcher, a golden Desert Eagle, and the devastating RPG rocket. Additionally, there are a variety of helpful pick-ups including a pair of Infrared goggles, a teleporter, the jetpack, and a gas mask. The aliens have put their hybridization system to good use; they&#8217;ve created an army of twenty ravenous creatures including mutant gorillas and chimpanzees, Hunter Killer Babes, and Hoglodytes. Making their glorious return from other versions are the infamous Octabrains and Pig Cops. The alien scum will pay for taking Duke&#8217;s women! Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes also features 25 cinematic sequences that capture the outcome of each mission and advance the storyline. There&#8217;s also a special blooper reel that can be unlocked with a little bit of skill. While the actual game is played from a third-person perspective, the multiplayer options incorporate a first-person viewpoint with a split screen for two players. It supports the Dual Shock Analog Controller and a memory card for saving game data. Product Highlights Video Product Identifiers Game Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes MPN 742725207103 UPC 742725207103 Key Features Platform Sony PlayStation 1 ESRB Rating M &#8211; Mature Genre Shooter Location USA Tech Details ESRB Descriptor Animated Blood &#038; Gore, Animated Violence, Strong Sexual Content Control Elements Gamepad/Joystick Number of Players 1-2 Release Year 2000 Game Special Features Take the role of the Duke and blast your way through 20 different levels featuring a variety of hidden areas Blast on a variety of enemies as you attempt to complete 14 unique missions Take down your enemies and rescue a variety of beautiful blondes, redheads, and brunettes View on eBay</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/duke-nukem-land-of-the-babes-playstation-1/">Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes &#8211; PlayStation 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br>Price:28.99 <br><img width="600" height="601" src="/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/1487801677_s-l1600_700x700_thumb.jpg" class="attachment-full size-full wp-post-image" alt="" style="float:left; margin:0 15px 15px 0;" /><hr /> Huge selection of new &#038; used video games. Great deals. Free shipping on all orders. 30-day money-back guarantee. We have everything from Atari to PS4. </p>
<hr />
 </p>
<div class="itemAttr">
<div class="section">
<h2 class="secHd">Item specifics</h2>
<table width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Condition:</td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<!-- ITEM CONDITION  --> 														<!-- If Attribute is having hidden text / link	 -->			 															</p>
<div aria-live="polite"> 															 															 																Good: <span id="vi-cond-addl-info">An item in used but good condition. May have minor damage to jewel case including scuffs or cracks, </span> 																</td>
<p> 																		 																		<!-- TODO: remove hardcoded ID --> 																		</td>
</p></div>
<p> 															 														<!-- </td>

 --> 													</td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Platform: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Sony PlayStation 1</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Rating: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>M &#8211; Mature</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Release Year: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>2000</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Genre: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Shooter</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			MPN: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="mpn">742725207103</h2>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			Game Name: </td>
<td width="30.0%"> 												<span>Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes</span></td>
<td class="attrLabels"> 									 			UPC: </td>
<td width="30.0%">
<h2 itemprop="gtin13">742725207103</h2>
</td>
</tr>
<p> 							<!-- Added for see review link --> 							</table>
</p></div></div>
<p>Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes (Sony PlayStation 1, 2000) &#8212; FREE SHIPPING!!</p>
<div class="prodDetailDesc">
<div class="prodDetailSec">
<div class="section-ttl">
<h3 class="p_det_title">Detailed item info</h3>
<div class="rd-sep"></div>
</div>
<table width="100%">
<tr>
<td><?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?></p>
<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" border="0" width="100%">
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Information</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Duke Nukem has finally scored his dream mission: to protect a gorgeous group of babes whiles saving the world. The Unified Babe Resistance is a group of escapees running from an alien colony&#8217;s hybridization wrath. These aliens are set for a full-scale invasion on Earth with an agenda including the eradication of the male population and the enslaving of beautiful women. It&#8217;s time to rock.</p>
<p>Featuring high-resolution 3D environments, Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes is a third-person adventure filled with alien scum and lots of babes. With four unique training areas and six multiplayer arenas, a total of 24 levels included (14 of which are actual missions). Utilizing his time portal, Duke will traverse through alien landscapes, intricate sewer systems, warehouses, and the ever-popular strip clubs in which he frequents.</p>
<p>In addition to optional auto aiming, Duke will automatically open doors and climb upon short ledges.This allows the player to focus on the more important aspects of the game such as rescuing babes and solving puzzles. Duke can also swim through water, climb up ladders and walls, and explore the confines of zero gravity movement.</p>
<p>Rather than featuring a conventional health system, Duke is judged by an all-new Ego system. Depending on his actions, the Ego meter will either rise after finishing a specific mission or drop on a misfired babe. Think before you shoot&#8230;Duke and the world&#8217;s survival is depending on it.</p>
<p>Remaining true to the series, Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes supplies you with a heavy arsenal of weaponry including the blaster, grenade launcher, a golden Desert Eagle, and the devastating RPG rocket. Additionally, there are a variety of helpful pick-ups including a pair of Infrared goggles, a teleporter, the jetpack, and a gas mask.</p>
<p>The aliens have put their hybridization system to good use; they&#8217;ve created an army of twenty ravenous creatures including mutant gorillas and chimpanzees, Hunter Killer Babes, and Hoglodytes. Making their glorious return from other versions are the infamous Octabrains and Pig Cops. The alien scum will pay for taking Duke&#8217;s women!</p>
<p>Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes also features 25 cinematic sequences that capture the outcome of each mission and advance the storyline. There&#8217;s also a special blooper reel that can be unlocked with a little bit of skill. While the actual game is played from a third-person perspective, the multiplayer options incorporate a first-person viewpoint with a split screen for two players. It supports the Dual Shock Analog Controller and a memory card for saving game data.</font><br class="br"/><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Highlights</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Video</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<div id="webyclipEmbeded" webyclip-product-page-title="Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes (Sony PlayStation 1, 2000)" webyclip-product-name="duke nukem: land of the babes sony playstation 1" webyclip-external-id="2980" webyclip-category="Video Games" webyclip-subcategory="US"></div>
<p><script type="text/javascript"> (function() { var s = document.createElement('script'); s.type = 'text/javascript'; s.async = true; s.src = (("https:" == document.location.protocol) ? "https://6bf746ad5bc91a240a3d-1d8fbdf7ecdc2b67730d7c561f0d1dfd.ssl.cf2.rackcdn.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js" : "http://code.webyclip.com/webyclip-ebay-pdp-default-loader.min.js"); var x = document.getElementsByTagName('script')[0]; x.parentNode.insertBefore(s, x); })(); </script></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Product Identifiers</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">MPN</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">742725207103</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">UPC</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">742725207103</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Key Features</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Platform</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Sony PlayStation 1</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Rating</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">M &#8211; Mature</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Genre</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Shooter</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Location</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">USA</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"><b>Tech Details</b></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">ESRB Descriptor</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Animated Blood &#038; Gore, Animated Violence, Strong Sexual Content</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Control Elements</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Gamepad/Joystick</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Number of Players</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">1-2</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Release Year</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">2000</font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="35%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2">Game Special Features</font></td>
<td width="65%" valign="top"><font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" size="2"></p>
<li>Take the role of the Duke and blast your way through 20 different levels featuring a variety of hidden areas
<li>Blast on a variety of enemies as you attempt to complete 14 unique missions
<li>Take down your enemies and rescue a variety of beautiful blondes, redheads, and brunettes
<p></font></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><br class="br"/></td>
</tr>
</table>
</td>
</tr>
</table></div></div>
<p> <a href="http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?ff3=2&#038;toolid=10039&#038;campid=5337897552&#038;item=172388214736&#038;vectorid=229466">View on eBay </a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW/product/duke-nukem-land-of-the-babes-playstation-1/">Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes &#8211; PlayStation 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/VGW">Video Game Warehouse</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/VGW/product/duke-nukem-land-of-the-babes-playstation-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	
<product>
	<price>28.99 </price>
<image>/VGW/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/1487801677_s-l1600-300x300.jpg</image>
</product>

	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
